Nathan Schneider

Web Developer

Personal Info

Address

22 Brookmeadow N Ln SW Apt 3 Grandville, MI 49418

Phone

(616) 803-9803

E-mail

nlschneider@gmail.com

WWW

http://nschneider.info

GitHub

https://github.com/nathanlschneider

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nathanlschneider

Skills

Javascript

HTML

CSS / SCSS

Responsive Web Design

Node

React

I'm a developer with a lifelong passion for learning, creating, technology and the arts. From playing the guitar and performing music, to coding, building computers or wrenching on my car, my interests encompass a wide range of areas. Growing up I was the type of kid that needed to take everything apart to see how it worked. As an adult, that still holds true. Getting the opportunity to learn new skills and deep dive into how things work is what I love and is something I enjoy in my spare time and in my career.

Experience

2015-09 IT Support & Development

Meritage Hospitality Group

Ivanti Service Manager Administration & Development

Full Stack Web Development

Workday Integration

Aloha POS Systems Support.

2013-01 - Remote Service Technician - Level II

2015-08 Support.com

Level II Home Networking Support (HNS) for Comcast.

Education

2011 - Grand Rapids Community College

2014 IT - Systems Administration

CIS - Computer Programming

Certificates

2018-03 ASD.1x: Agile Software Development

https://courses.edx.org/certificates/04f2056115074150927839bf407ffa85

2018-08 Web Developer Bootcamp

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-JZ7LBJDJ/

Courses

Advanced Visual Basic.NET Programming CO 225

Advanced Windows Operating System CO 205

C++ Programming CO 127

HTML Essentials CO 148

Internet Scripting CO 247

Introduction to C# Programming CO 129

Introduction to Computer Information Systems CO 110

Local Area Networking CO 233

Principles of Information Security CO 212

UNIX Operating System CO 132

UNIX Shell Programming CO 142

UNIX/LINUX Systems Administration CO 232

Visual Basic.NET Programming CO 124

Web Design Fundamentals CO 146

Wide Area Networking (WAN) Theory CO 231